gnatta.com 2016-05-31

# Privacy Policy | Gnatta

This cookie and privacy policy covers the Gnatta.com website Felicitas Media and its website. We are committed to protecting your privacy, and at the same time we endeavour to use any data we collect from you to provide the best possible service.

## Providing visitors with anonymous access

You can access our website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

## Automatic collection of information using cookies

We use cookies on the website to track visitor behaviour and store certain site preferences. If you prefer not to allow the use of cookies, you can change the configuration of your browser to either warn you when you receive a cookie, or to automatically reject them. You may find, however, that disabling cookies means certain areas of the site do not function correctly.

If you would like to find out more about cookies, including how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance.

## What are cookies?

Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites. They are used by most websites to tailor information and marketing messages to better suit your needs, as well as to store login or personal information for your convenience.

## Types of cookie used on our website

Session Cookies - We use a session cookie to remember your login and access permissions. These we deem strictly necessary to the working of the website. If these are disabled then various functionalities on the site will be inaccessible via your browser.

Google Analytics – We use this to understand how the website is being used in order to improve the user experience. User data is anonymous.

## Facebook

We use the Facebook API services to access publicly available Facebook content

We always acquire express permission and ensure permission has expressly granted by the owners of Facebook accounts, before using the Facebook API to gather any content related to their Facebook account.

Facebook data which has been downloaded to the Gnatta application will never be shared with or used by any third parties or applications outside of the Gnatta application.

All data downloaded via the Facebook API will be used strictly for the purposes of providing customer services to Facebook users who first seek our assistance (customer services provided on behalf of our customers).

We will always comply with the privacy policies specified by Facebook and will make every effort to remain complaint as directed.

If any individual or company requests information related to themselves to be deleted we will comply immediately provided they provide reasonable identification upon with any deletion request. If we are required by law to keep copies of any deleted data, we will keep and archive which is not visible through our application.

We will never post Ad's on Facebook from our application, or otherwise display ad's relating to any data dowloaded form Facebook.

We will never store or use 'friend data' or track people or account related to any Facebook account or individual.

## Data collection and use

We do not collect personal data from Facebook, other than the users Facebook name/alias and their thumbnail picture.

We may use data downloaded from Facebook for research and development or customer administration, but will never use gathered information for marketing purposes.

We do not collect or use personal data for any other purpose, nor do we share it with third parties. However, if we wish to use Facebook data for a new purpose, we will always ask permission first.

## Confidentiality & security

We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send personal data via our website (secure SSL connection).

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

  * Unauthorized access
  * Improper use or disclosure
  * Unauthorized modification
  * Unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors that have access to, and are associated with, the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your personal data.

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to state institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

## Access to the personal data we may hold

Anyone person or company is entitled by law to request a copy of any personal data we hold about them. If you would like to know whether we hold personal information about you or your company, please contact us by emailing info@felicitasmedia.com

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data that we keep about you within a week. To enable us to release any data, we may require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge.

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you or your company and, where appropriate, you may have the data:

  * Completed
  * Rectified or amended
  * Erased

## The services and links of our website

Our website does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others, other than through participation in our forum pages.

## Privacy compliance

Our privacy policy is compliant with the Data Protection Act 1998 UK, and we are committed to a procedure of self-assessment to ensure we continue to comply.

## Queries

If you have any other queries relating to your privacy and the use of your personal data, please contact:

Data and Privacy Policy Enquiries

HEAD OFFICE  
Felicitas Media Limited  
Media Village  
131-151 Great Titchfield Street  
London, W1W 5BB  
United Kingdom
